// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1) Choose the MASCULINE gender",
    answer: "Father",
    options: [
      "Mother",
      "Father",
       "Teacher",
      "Tree"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "2) Choose the FEMININE  gender",
    answer: "Queen",
    options: [
      "King",
      "Boy",
       "Doctor",
      "Queen"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "3) Choose the COMMON gender",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "student",
      "Teacher",
       "Police",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "4) select the NEUTER gender.",
    answer: "Book",
    options: ["Parents",
      "Uncle",
       "Aunty",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "5) Find the odd one out?",
    answer: "Neighbours",
    options: [
      "Pen",
      "Shoes",
       "Car",
      "Neighbours"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "6) Grandmother represents ________ gender.",
    answer: "Feminine",
    options: [
      "Feminine",
      "Masculine",
       "Common",
      "Neuter"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "7) Uncle refers to _________ gender.",
    answer: "Masculine",
    options: [
      "Feminine",
      "Masculine",
       "Common",
      "Neuter"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "8) Knife  is a _________ gender.",
    answer: "Neuter",
    options: [
      "Feminine",
      "Masculine",
       "Common",
      "Neuter"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "9) Teacher is a _________ gender.",
    answer: "Common",
    options: [ "Feminine",
      "Masculine",
       "Common",
      "Neuter"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "10) Find the odd one out.",
    answer: "Police",
    options: [
      "God",
      "Actor",
       "Brother",
      "Police"
    ]
  },
];